Flying Home is a romance film directed by Dominique Deruddere.
Colin, an ambitious young American businessman, has a deal with a potential
client, a rich Arab sheikh who is a passionate pigeon fancier.
The sheikh has tried several times to buy a champion pigeon, but
the owner continues to stubbornly refuse his offer.
In an attempt to gain the trust of the Sheikh, Colin offers him a deal: if he manages to convince the
owner to sell the champion pigeon, the sheikh will agree to do business with Colin's company.
But when Colin meets Jos, the grumpy owner of the pigeon, and Isabella, his
granddaughter, he realizes that this mission will not be as easy as he had hoped.
Colin, played by Jamie Dornan.
Isabelle Pauwels, played by Charlotte De Bruyne.
Jos Pauwels, played by Jan Decleir.
Sheikh, played by Ali Suliman.
Priest, played by Josse De Pauw.
Martha, played by Viviane de Muynck.
Flying Home (a.k.a.
Racing Hearts) is a 2014 romantic drama film directed by Dominique
Deruddere and also written by Dominique Deruddere.
The film was released in 2 April 2014.
The film explores themes of grandfather, betrayal, pigeon.
The tone is emotional.